Wesley Orr

524 West 18th Street, Kearney, NE 68845 • (308) 464-1557 • wesleyorr3@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/wesley-orr-67465b160/ • https://github.com/wes214

Professional Summary

Detailed oriented and highly adaptable professional with experience in web development, Windows systems administration, and Cisco networking systems. A passion for learning new technologies and placing myself in situations where I can learn new skills. My interest includes cyber security and software developing where I have experience in multiple projects and course work.

Education

Bachelor of Science: Management Information Systems, 2019

University Of Nebraska At Kearney - Kearney, NE

Work Experience

Intern Web Developer, 10/2018 to Current

Chief Industries - Grand Island, NE

- Deployed highly interactive web applications utilizing AngularJS 2+, Type Script and integrating Restful API's
- Worked in an Agile collaborative environment designing code and testing innovative applications
- Provided creative solutions which exceeded the expectations of clients
- Debugged web applications using web developer tools on Chrome

Intern Desktop Support/ Software Technician, 05/2017 to 10/2018

Chief Industries - Grand Island, NE

- Maintained reliability, stability and data integrity of the Oracle databases
- Wrote PL/SQL scripts for company auditing and workplace automation
- Managed security permissions for all user accounts on production applications
- Developed and managed internal services running a Windows environment
- Performed Troubleshooting on end user hardware and software issues

LAN Manager, 11/2015 to Current

Army National Guard NE - Omaha, NE

- Responsible for maintaining, processing and troubleshooting computer systems and operations
- Provided computer system administration, local area network administration
- Configured and implemented subnet IP addresses for computers on local network along with routers and switches
- Performed network connectivity troubleshooting, hardware and software issues
- Constructed testing and editing on computer programs

Skills

- Python
- JavaScript
- HTML/CSS
- Java

- Angular 2+
- React
- Django
- Active DoD Secret Clearance